START WITH RAW,
UNEDITED CLIPS, JUST
A BUNCH OF
FILES IN A
FOLDER. BUT WITH
DIRECTOR'S CUT, YOU
CAN TURN THOSE
FILES INTO A
PROFESSIONAL EDIT IN
MOMENTS. IT'S AN
AGENTIC VIDEO EDITOR
THAT LIVES RIGHT
IN YOUR TERMINAL,
USE THE DOCTOR
COMMAND TO CHECK
YOUR SETUP, THEN
JUST DESCRIBE THE
VIDEO YOU WANT.
THE AI ANALYZES
YOUR FOOTAGE, MAKES
CREATIVE DECISIONS, AND
HANDLES THE RENDERING.
LOOK AT THAT.
PERFECTLY TIMED CUTS,
NARRATION, AND OVERLAYS.
YOU'RE NOT JUST
GETTING AN MP4.
YOU GET THE
SCRIPTS, THE AUDIO,
AND THE PROJECT
DATA. EVERY AI
DECISION IS TRANSPARENT
AND EDITABLE IN
THIS JSON FILE,
GIVING YOU TOTAL
CONTROL. THE WORKFLOW
IS MODULAR. YOU
CAN GENERATE JUST
THE VIDEO FIRST,
THEN LAYER ON
THE NARRATION AND
BURN IN WORD
-BY -WORD SUBTITLES
FOR SOCIAL MEDIA.
FOR EFFICIENT COST,
USE CHATTERBOX FOR
LOCAL ON -DEVICE
VOICE CLONING AND
TEXT TO SPEECH.
FROM ONE SET
OF FOOTAGE, YOU
CAN CREATE INFINITE
VARIATIONS JUST BY
CHANGING YOUR NATURAL
LANGUAGE PROMPT. SPEND
LESS TIME EDITING
AND MORE TIME
CREATING. THIS IS
DIRECTOR'S CUT.